你好 我叫福雷斯 福雷斯甘
Hello. My name's Forrest - Forrest Gump.
要吃巧克力吗?
Do you want a chocolate?
我能吃掉上百万块巧克力
I could eat about a million and a half of these.
我妈妈常说
My mama always said
人生就像一盒各式各样的巧克力
Life was like a box of chocolates.
你永远不知道下一块将会是哪种
You never know what you're going to get.
那双鞋子一定很舒适
Those must be comfortable shoes.
穿这样的鞋子你可以走上一整天
I bet you could walk all day in shoes like that
脚都不会痛
and not feel a thing.
我希望能有一双这样的鞋子
I wish I had shoes like that.
其实我的脚很痛
My feet hurt .
妈妈常说要想知道一个人的很多事情
Mama always said there's an awful lot
只要看看他穿的鞋就能知道
you can tell about a person by their shoes.
他会往哪里走
Where they're going,
他住在哪里
where they've been.
我穿过很多双鞋子
I've worn lots of shoes.
如果我仔细想的话
I bet if I think about it real hard
我能记得我第一双鞋子的模样
I could remember my first pair of shoes.
妈妈说它会带我到任何地方
Mama said they'd take me anywhere .
她说它是双魔鞋
She said they was my magic shoes.